If we can recover the imperial seal
Если мы сможем вернуть императорскую печать
For us
для нас это
It would be heaven's mercy
будет благословением небес
But fortune and misfortune are intertwined
Но беда и удача идут рядом
This seal is also a hot potato
Эта печать  горячая картошка
The longer we stay in Yiyang
Чем дольше мы задержимся в Ияне
The more likely things will change
тем больше риск перемен
Once we get the seal
Как только получим печать
Seal the news immediately
немедленно засекретим информацию
We'll claim illness
сошлёмся на болезнь
And return south quickly
и быстро вернёмся на юг
Yes
Есть
Come, come
Давайте давайте
Today Prince of Jin is hosting a banquet
Сегодня князь Цзинь устроил пир
Everyone gets to enjoy it too
и нам тоже перепало
Brothers
Братцы
Come
давайте
Have a drink, have a drink
выпьем
Drinking at this time
Сейчас пить
Gives us some benefit
Дали нам чтото хорошее
Boosts morale
поднять боевой дух
Don't worry about what the higher-ups think
Не думай что скажет начальство
This wine is the real deal
Вино настоящее
Come, come
Давайте давайте
Come, bottoms up
Давай пей
Bottoms up
Пей
Everyone, keep drinking
Пейте ребята
I'll send some to the other brothers too
я отнесу братьям в другие места
At the banquet
На пиру
You toast back and forth with Chu Maolun
ты пил с Чу Маолунем
After three rounds
После трёх кругов
Chu Maolun urgently goes to relieve himself
Чу Маолунь сослался на нужду и ушёл
But even the soldiers guarding him
но вместе с охранявшими его солдатами
Disappear together
исчез
Just as you're lost in fantasies about the seal
Пока ты был погружён в мечты о печати
The city gates are opened by traitors under cover of night
городские ворота были ночью открыты предателем